

AGA BOLOZ

Assistant manager

About me

A passionate, resourceful and optimistic professional with an array of skills that would be an asset to any company. My experiences in Hospitality, Project and Business Management and Teaching have been wide and varied which has seen me work in many different industries with different people from all walks of life.

Contacts

- 20 West Ave, NW42LJ London
- § 07747 230299
- □ aggy.boloz@gmail.com

Skills

- ☆ Willingness to learn
- ☆ Productivity
- ☆ Computer literate
- ☆ Leadership skills
- ☆ Attention to detail and accuracy
- ☆ Organization skills
- ☆ Decision-making
- ☆ Team work
- ☆ Confidence and drive
- ☆ Customer service
- ☆ Excellent communication

Education

Graduate Diploma in International Coaching Studies

The Bogdan Janski Academy between 2013-2014

Graduate Diploma in Social Economy Management

Academy of Entrepreneurship and Marketing between 2012-2013

Graduate Diploma in Journalism and Media Communication

The Jagiellonian University between 2010-2011

B.A. in Polish Philology - Teaching major

The Jagiellonian Univeristy between 2005-2008

Experience

Assistant Manager, Pret a Manger, London

July 2015 - March 2020

Analysing and forecasting shop sales levels and profitability

Preparing reports at the end of the shift/week, including staff control, food control and sales

Coordinating the operation of the shop ensuring that kitchen and shop floor staff are working as a team

Recruiting, training and managing my team

Providing feedback and coaching to the team regularly

Responding to customer queries and complaints

Maintaining high standards of hygiene, health and safety by conducting management checks and reporting any action taken

Managing stock levels and making key decisions about stock control

Ordering supplies, checking the quality and quantity of deliveries and managing invoices

Ensuring wide selection and great quality of products is offered to the customers along with excellent customer service

Arranging for new employees' proper onboarding

Demonstrating basic HR knowledge (conduct, performance, sickness etc.)

Arranging for maintenance and repair of equipment and other services.

Calculating and driving productivity of the team

Conducting team briefs and staff meetings

Setting up fixed and on demand production, controlling waste

Reviewing MS reports and NPS scores regularly

Demonstrating knowledge of KPI's

Point of Sale Cashier, Nandos, London

December 2014 - June 2015

Delivering great customer service during high-volume, fast-paced operations and prioritizing guest experience as top priority

Effectively communicating with peers to navigate the duties and responsibilities expected

Supporting the development of peers through guiding, training and coaching team members

Handling currency and credit transactions quickly and accurately.

 $\label{eq:monitoring} \mbox{Monitoring storage, preparation, cooking, handling, and serving of food}$

Assisting management with inventory control and stock ordering

Project Manager, Mloda Lomnica Association, Lomnica Zdroj, Poland

April 2011 - December 2014

Coordinating the activities of the project, including project design, developing methodology and overseeing implementation

Coordinating a flexible project team bringing in topical specialists, as required

Qualifications

- ☑ EITCA Information Technologies
 Telework Competencies Certificate –
 October 2013
- ☑ EITCA Information TechnologiesKey Competencies Certificate –April 2014
- Manager of Social Economy − March -July 2013
- Financial Management for NGOs

 Course December 2012
- Project Management for NGOs
 Course December 2012
- Fundraising and Applying for Grants for NGOs Course December
- Promoting the NGOs Course December 2012

Interests



Planning and delegating work with tasks, subtasks, folders, templates, workflows, calendars, dashboards, Gantt-Chart, timesheets and other essential tools

Managing the budget and accountability of finances

Reporting on project progress at internal and external meetings

Managing and troubleshooting project risks with a declared risk register, initiating corrective action where necessary

Providing reports, evaluations and assessing result of projects

Ensuring coherence and good cooperation within the project team and alignment of the different stakeholders and departments

Applying for grants and funding

Undertaking and initiating regular talks to supporters, agencies, donor groups, churches, schools and corporate partners to raise project awareness

Overlooking project visibility in social media

Coaching and motivating project teams

Thorough understanding and use of Microsoft Office suite together with some understanding and use of specialist project management software such as Trello, MS Project and Open Project.

Multiple Student Teacher Placement Positions, Lomnica Zdroj, Poland

June 2007 - April 2011

Secondary School Boleslaw Barbacki in Nowy Sacz, Poland, 2010 Primary School in Lomnica Zdroj, Poland, 2007 maj Julian Zubek Gymnasium in Lomnica Zdroj, Poland, 2007

I have an understanding the core principals of student teaching

The ability to connect with students, challenging learners intellectually and academically in a way that is relevant in the real world

I would be required to maintain the high expectations of the school, always applying academic rigor. As a student teacher I would be required to engage with students at all levels of schooling either struggling or over achieving I would need to identify this and tailor my focus accordingly.

Building relationships with my fellow student teachers/educators was vital for my development and growth learning from their professional experiences.

References

References are available upon request